export default {
  "id": 'G10Spanish-L3-CH4-1',
  "grade": 10,
  "subject": "Language Arts",
  "title": 'Spanish Chapter 4',
  "timeLimit": 30,
  "topic": "Spanish Chapter 4: Lesson 3",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "apple",
      "options": ["manzana", "pera", "naranja"],
      "correctAnswer": "manzana"
    },
    {
      "question": "dog",
      "options": ["gato", "perro", "caballo"],
      "correctAnswer": "perro"
    },
    {
      "question": "house",
      "options": ["casa", "escuela", "carro"],
      "correctAnswer": "casa"
    },
    {
      "question": "water",
      "options": ["agua", "fuego", "aire"],
      "correctAnswer": "agua"
    },
    {
      "question": "book",
      "options": ["mesa", "libro", "silla"],
      "correctAnswer": "libro"
    },
    {
      "question": "car",
      "options": ["carro", "bicicleta", "avi칩n"],
      "correctAnswer": "carro"
    },
    {
      "question": "school",
      "options": ["hospital", "casa", "escuela"],
      "correctAnswer": "escuela"
    },
    {
      "question": "sun",
      "options": ["sol", "luna", "estrella"],
      "correctAnswer": "sol"
    },
    {
      "question": "cat",
      "options": ["perro", "gato", "p치jaro"],
      "correctAnswer": "gato"
    },
    {
      "question": "chair",
      "options": ["silla", "mesa", "puerta"],
      "correctAnswer": "silla"
    },
    {
      "question": "to learn",
      "options": ["aprender", "comprender", "escribir"],
      "correctAnswer": "aprender"
    },
    {
      "question": "to understand",
      "options": ["comprar", "leer", "comprender"],
      "correctAnswer": "comprender"
    },
    {
      "question": "to teach",
      "options": ["ense침ar", "dibujar", "bailar"],
      "correctAnswer": "ense침ar"
    },
    {
      "question": "student",
      "options": ["profesor", "maestro", "estudiante"],
      "correctAnswer": "estudiante"
    },
    {
      "question": "homework",
      "options": ["tarea", "escribir", "escuchar"],
      "correctAnswer": "tarea"
    },
    {
      "question": "to study",
      "options": ["escuchar", "estudiar", "comer"],
      "correctAnswer": "estudiar"
    },
    {
      "question": "to read",
      "options": ["leer", "hablar", "bailar"],
      "correctAnswer": "leer"
    },
    {
      "question": "to write",
      "options": ["escribir", "dibujar", "aprender"],
      "correctAnswer": "escribir"
    },
    {
      "question": "pen",
      "options": ["pluma", "cuaderno", "libro"],
      "correctAnswer": "pluma"
    },
    {
      "question": "notebook",
      "options": ["libro", "cuaderno", "pupitre"],
      "correctAnswer": "cuaderno"
    }
  ]
};
